

# **LES BOGDAN**

PHP DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

During my 15-years of working in programming my own website www.jubuti.com and other little projects related to web developing, I have accumulated a lot of experience in PHP and JavaScript coding, and CSS styling. I look forward to new challenges in developing various websites because they make me better and intrigue me.

#### **CONTACT DETAILS**

- +40-724-154-222
- bogdan19802010@gmail.com
- Romania, Timis, Giarmata-Vii Str. Infratirea, No. 140A
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/bogdan-les-892636155 https://github.com/BogdanLes

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Jubuti.com

Owner and Developer | January 2008 - Present

- PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySql programmer for www.jubuti.com international business and professional database
- I am also working on developing other web related projects

#### **Gold for Gold**

Sales Consultant | September 2021 - March 2023

Consultation/Evaluation/Sale of gold and diamond jewelry

### ■ Timisoara International Airport

Merceologist | October 2000 - September 2003

• Supply Office - purchase of goods and services for the institution

#### **EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS**

2023

# The Informal School of IT

2024

Course: Java Development

Title: Junior software developer

Project: Web interface for a business database

- Procedural programming: variables, operators, clauses, loops, arrays, methods
- OOP: Classes, Objects, Interfaces, Enams, Abstraction, Encapsulation, Inheritance, Polymorphism, Composition, Design patterns

- Collections: ArrayList, LinkedList, HashSet, TreeSet, HashMap, TreeMap, Exception handling, Threads, Lamda
- File handling, XML, SQL, PostgreSQL
- · Maven, Intellij IDEA, Git, Github

#### 2023 W3Schools

Course: PHP

Title: PHP Developer

https://verify.w3schools.com/609023LF1

- Procedural programming: variables, operators, clauses, loops, arrays, functions, regular expressions, superglobals, exceptions, date, filters
- OOP: Classes, Objects, Interfaces, Abstraction, Encapsulation, Inheritance, Polymorphism, Traits, Iterables
- · Forms, AJAX, JSON, Cookies, Sessions
- File handling, XML, SimpleXML, XML DOM, SQL, MySQL

#### 2023 W3Schools

Course: C++

Title: C++ Developer

https://verify.w3schools.com/609023LF1

- Procedural programming: variables, operators, clauses, loops, arrays, functions, structures, enums, pointers
- OOP: Classes, Objects, Abstraction, Encapsulation, Inheritance, Polymorphism
- File handling

# 2004 | The West University of Timișoara

2006

Master's degree

Faculty of Economic Sciences

Specialization: Strategic Management of Organizations

Dissertation: Analysis of the strategies of Bancii Comerciale Romane S.A. in the period 2001-2004

- Management: principles, functions, styles
- Methods and techniques for evaluating businesses and products based on the market and competition

#### 2000 | Banat University

-2004

Bachelor's degree

Faculty of Economic Sciences

Specialization: Finance-Accounting

Title: Licensed Economist

Bachelor's thesis: Study on the use of fixed funds at S.C. Sabico-Impex SRL

- Accounting, Budget and taxation, Finance, Economic-financial analysis
- Marketing, Management, Statistics, Microeconomics, Macroeconomics, Capital markets

#### 1995 -2000

# **Grigore Moisil Informatics High School**

Baccalaureate diploma

Title: Junior software developer

• First contact with programming in Pascal and C++, and first interaction with a database FoxPro

# **SKILLS**

- PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, MySQL, XML, AJAX, JSON, jQuery, Apache, NetBeans, GIT
- C, C++, JAVA, Maven, IntelliJ IDEA, PostgreSQL, CodeBlocks, Software Design Patterns, Object-Oriented Programming
- Analytical Skills, Teamwork, Adaptability, Problem solving, Critical thinking, Creativity and Innovation, Self-Motivation and Initiative

# **LANGUAGES**

- Romanian (Native)
- English (Fluent)

# **HOBBIES**

• Football, Strategy Games, Fishing, Fitness